[
{
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐ฆ๐ป๐ชโกโโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ููููุง"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โหโโ๐ฆ๐ป๐ก๏ธโ๏ธ๐ฅโโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ููุชุงู"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐๐โโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ููุฑููู"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐ฆ๐ป๐ฆฏโโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ุบูู"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐ฉ๐ป๐๐ท๏ธโโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ุดูุฒููู"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐ฆ๐ป๐๏ธโ๏ธโโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ููุฑุงุจููุง"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐๐๐ท๏ธโโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ููุณููุง"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐๐โโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ูููู"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐ฉ๐ป๐๐ป๐๐ปโโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ุฑูุจูู"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐๐ฆ โโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ุชุดูุจุฑ"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โหโโ๐ฑ๐ผโโ๏ธ๐ก๏ธโ๏ธ๐งญ โโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ุฒูุฑู"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐๐ปโโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ุจุฑูู"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐ฉ๐ป๐ฉ๏ธ๐โโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ูุงูู"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐๐ช๐ป๐โโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ุฌููุจู"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐คฅ๐ฑ๐ฃโโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ุงูุณูุจ"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐ฉ๐ป๐๐ปโโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ูุงูููู"
    } ,
 {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โหโโ๐ฑ๐ผโโ๏ธ๐ถ๏ธ๐ก๏ธ๐คโโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ูุฑุงููู"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐จ๐ผโ๐ณ๐คธ๐ผโโ๏ธ๐ฌโโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ุณุงูุฌู"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โ- อชชฬฅหโโ๐ฑ๐ผโโ๏ธ๐ฉ๐ฅโโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ุณุงุจู"
    }, 
   {
        "question": "ูู ุงูุดุฎุตูุฉ โหโโ๐ฒ๐ง๐ปโโโ๏ธโโห อชชฬฅ",
        "response": "ูุงูุฏู"
    }
     
]
